{
    "id": "44ad798c761845899d266ae745525241",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Both my sisters ………………………. married.",
            "description": "Use a plural noun and a plural verb after both. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She had a child holding on to each ………………………….",
            "description": "Use a singular noun after each.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "hands"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We should help ………………………….",
            "description": "Use each other to talk about two people or things use one another to talk about more than two people or things. ",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers love …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not as brilliant as ……………………………….",
            "description": "Either him or he is is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "he is"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Your car is faster than …………………………..",
            "description": "Your car is faster than mine means the same as your car is faster than my car. ",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Your essay is better than ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Both Sam and Manual ……………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after both.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You and ……………………….. have nothing to fear.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the subject should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us …………………………….. seen him since then.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after none.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is better ………………………….. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. by friends, we lost all hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Deceived",
                "Deceiving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}